Hello guys welcome to another video stock
market nice ICICI Lombard General
Insurance's June quarter final
result of totka which will be
covered today friends let's
start the video guys here is the
differential result of the company there has been growth in the June quarter
now we will first talk about the company's
result which I will convert it into cards by garlic numbers and
tell you about the
income it has a gross income of 3908 crores
whereas in the previous quarter the
income was 70 crores and
in the jun21 quarter it had fallen to 38 points and the
online form was generated so this time the
income quantum is very much down but the
income tax which is being seen increasing this time will be
talked about for reference the expenses of this company
this time is 60 crores whereas
in the previous quarter it was much bigger than this
and in the jun21 quarter it was 36
crores special you can see the company has
more income the space of the company is  The company
law board company was continuously seeing losses
but now the students here who
can see the operating profit, the flight profit of the company, where the profit of the company is around, which is
more than this profit, which is a profit of 121 crores in this quarter
and 100 crores in June 21 pot and the
profit quarter of the company and
in comparison of both, a slight increase was being seen this year, the
performance of this company is being seen very strong this time, if we
talk about history, then it is
1.1 ₹1, which is being seen
this time from both the previous quarter and the player, that
means this year starts,
that is being seen, guys,
as if the company is showing good promise,
now if we talk about the
companies of one segment here, then the company
generates biography of three scenes here, one net
premium on second anthem for investment
and The Amazing Spider-Man
comes here, you can say
subscribe motor and you can watch here
Now the
school which you
can see here,
you can see it well by the number, so
you
can see it here and if we talk about
New Delhi Foreign then here the
difficulty which was seen working from last year to this time was
but it is being
seen now we will do it
if you say bye-bye in the comment box